https://ctftime.org/writeup/19131

This is the writeup for the logon challenge in picoCTF 2019. 

The solutions goes, 

The website only checks for the passwor of Joe. Meaning with any other accounts we can login.
After loging in with an abtritary username and password we see that we have succesfully logged in. 
But we don't see the flag, well if you click Home tab and capture the request
You can see in the cookie that it has 3 variables, pass, user, and admin. 
We just need to set the admin to True, because I think Joe's account is the admine, that's why his password is more secure.


